[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "Do you have the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "I do not, Piers, but I do believe that we may reach a point where the markets have to tell us to come through an agreement and that would be of course when we start defaulting on our debts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2010"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VB", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 29, "question": "How do you bring the two together and get some kind of common sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "To be honest, I don't know, because I say it with respect to those individuals who say defund or nothing else, although they have changed their message somewhat it used to be just absolute defunding, now apparently it's already if you just address certain portions of ObamaCare, but look there was a lot of republican members of congress who campaigned in 2010 and said, \"You send me there, I'll do everything in my power to defund ObamaCare.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "If you were Speaker Boehner, what would you do now to try and get through this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I think it's very difficult for me to say because I'm a great admirer of the speaker and it's very tough given the divisions within his conference.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "At what point does that political stunt which gets perfectly understandable becomes against the national interest particularly with the debt ceiling coming up so fast?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I would -- If were the president, I look at my own polls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "But why should the conversation start with a metaphorical gun to his head?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Because it's on both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "INGRICH: Well, Barack Obama ain't no Bill Clinton, so what's the point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, the point is staying on both houses.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "I don't know (inaudible), will you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "I'm real good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "I could be any animal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yeah, you love animals that's why we're here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "An elephant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "They have 105,000 muscles in their trunk.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "You want 105,000 muscles in your trunk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "And they're big and they last a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "So you're basically basing -- and this is based on Newt, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, no actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Have you found that British person who said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "That was the decisive moment, Pier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What is your most common argument at home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "The public are sick and tired of this, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Dispute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well, you have to call Van Jones (ph) to come around and ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "And the moment I heard that, I thought, \"This is the guy,\" because if you can get out of a straitjacket, we can get out of this shutdown, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "''", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I look at it this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "And you are going to come back with me with a straitjacket, a bit later, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "I'm going to put you in a straitjacket.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Very quickly, you got a new show, Believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes, it's on Spike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "CD", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Ma'am?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Yes, you know, you two do similar jobs that just make the economy sense for you to go, Dan (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Good evening, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, you must think you're either a soothsayer or you're just so long in the tooth in this Washington game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Armando Iannucci"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", ":", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I mean what do you make and what's going on now, particularly, as you've lampooned this so successfully?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, I must say Armando Iannucci who said -- really brilliant creative guy behind writing Veep, has this uncanny ability, particularly, since he is after all British, to predict, but you may have this ability too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "``", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Can you remember one that has been (inaudible) hot over one side trying to dismantle and establish law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "-NONE-", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No, I don't think there's any parallel to this, you know, Secretary (inaudible), I thought, got something slightly off in the earlier segment when he said that, \"There was no particular law involved in the previous conflict in the Gingrich-Clinton standoff because there was one similarity, it was about -- the budget was about Medicare.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "The sense -- because, you know, midterms coming up, and you have the big election in 2016, it can't be helpful, can it, the chances of doing one and either of those two elections if they are seen to be absolutely ideologically at each other's throats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, I think you're right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "TIME": ["Night"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "ORGAN: Is there anything you couldn't parity, Frank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "There's nothing that you can't parity and we know it from shows not just like Veep in Saturday Night Live, but so many shows in American television.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You think they've ever going to grow up in Washington?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Edwin"]}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "And why do you believe the real victim may, will be, Edwin and not as many people think Alexian Lien who was of course the driver of the SUV?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", ",", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, Piers, Edwin is clearly a victim.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edwin", "Alexian Lien"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What's his condition at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "He's out of his comma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What is your view about where blames should lie here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I mean I wasn't there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What would you want to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I think, I would have stopped and I would have tried to get the information for the insurance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "What do you think, Dayana?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "They hadn't done anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dayana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 544, "question": "How many bikers do you see in this video, 3 -- 400, 500 bikers or 20?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", ":", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Enough not to...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Why would you be scared?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Because I would be very concerned...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Do we have evidence of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "And that this is my point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Is there evidence to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "All right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Do you see them already banging and hitting this vehicle before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I see hundreds of bikes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "But dozens -- I mean, how many it will take to be scary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "(Inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131007pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "And anyway, how are you Criss Angel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I will say that I'm going to leave you like the couple moments leaving us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]